Narrator: Visit Scotland
Speaker: Scotland is one of the world’s top tourist destinations, with 10,000 kilometres of coast,
790 islands, more than 30,000 ‘lochs’ (the word in Scotland for lakes), famous castles,
and beautiful cities.
There’s something for visitors of all ages.
Narrator: Why Loch Ness?
Speaker: Loch Ness is 10 km south west of the city of Inverness – perfect for day trips.
You can take a boat trip on the loch and visit the Loch Ness Centre to find out all about ‘Nessie’, the monster.
One of the most beautiful castles in the world, Urquhart Castle, is on the banks of the loch.
There are wonderful places for walking and cycling very near.
Narrator: Accommodation
Speaker: Stay at the Craigdarroch Hotel. It’s the perfect place for a great view of the loch.